BU Records: Rufus B. Spain, Inclusive: 1960-2012, undated, Bulk: 2002-2011
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Retirement: Subject Files, Inclusive: 1986-2007, undated, Bulk: 2002-2005; 3
  - Vision 2012: Draft: Long Version, circa 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Vision 2012: Letter to Baylor University Board of Regents, 2003 May 6 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - “Where is Baylor Headed Religiously?”: Essay, circa 2004 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Retirement: Literary Productions, Inclusive: 1985-2012, Bulk: 2003-2012; 4
  As in Series II and Series III, the materials in this final series were collected and produced after Rufus Spain’s retirement from teaching at Baylor. This series contains newspaper clippings and magazine articles, many of them closely related to the Baylor 2012 plan, as well as often-annotated newsletters of the Baylor Retired Professors/Administrators Program. This series is in good condition.
  - Articles and Clippings: Index for Baylor News, 2003-2010 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Articles and Clippings: Index for The Baylor Lariat, 2003-2012 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Articles and Clippings: Index for The Dallas Morning News, 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Articles and Clippings: Index for The Waco Tribune-Herald, 2003-2012 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Articles, Clippings, and Correspondence: General (1 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1985-2012 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Articles, Clippings, and Correspondence: General (2 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1985-2012 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Articles, Clippings, and Correspondence: General (3 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1985-2012 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Articles, Clippings, and Correspondence: General (4 of 4) [RESTRICTED], 1985-2012 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 1998 October-December (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters: Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program, 2012 January-October (Box 14, Folder 18)